Dale Graham

Personable and Extroverted Computer Science Student with a passion for creating, innovating, and learning. Experience with coding and developing in both individual and team settings. A naturally fast learner, often recognized for creative and unique problem solving abilities. Proficiency in Java and beginner knowledge in HTML, CSS, and UX Design.

EDUCATION

The University of North Carolina at Charlotte, Charlotte, NC January 2019 - Present B.A in Computer Science, Information Technology Concentration

Anticipated Graduation Date: Spring 2022

 Current GPA: 3.869/4 Dean's List: Spring 2021

Central Piedmont Community College, Charlotte, NC July 2017- December 2019

A.A in Biology

Graduation: Fall 2019 Dean's List: Fall 2018

EXPERIENCE

Riddle and Bloom - Amazon Prime Student, Charlotte, NC August 2021-Present Campus Manager

- Conduct Prime Student pitches in person and virtually
- Use professional connections to host events and pitches with campus organizations and clubs
- Participate in online group chats, maintaining daily communication with company, connections, and fellow Campus Managers

Good Times CLT, Charlotte, NC November 2019 - Present

Retail Sales Associate

- Identify, develop, and share processes which could be both improved and standardized.
- Collaborate with team members to build and sustain a solid social media presence.
- Demonstrate a consistent working knowledge of business and industry trends.
- Assist customers with purchases and insight through product knowledge.

Publix Super Markets, Charlotte, NC November 2016- January 2020

Customer Service Staff

- Accounted daily transactions and ensured the accurate balance of all registers
- Assisted team with problem solving by serving as an escalation point for customer concerns.
- Provided leadership and direction to team members to ensure the standardized completion of daily tasks
- Applied job knowledge effectively to solve routine customer concerns

Charlotte, NC 28269

(980) 345-0770

dalecsgraham@gmail.com LinkedIn: Dale Graham GitHub: Dale Graham

SKILLS

- -Java (2+ Years), MySQL, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- -Wireframing
- -High and Low Fidelity Prototyping
- -Responsive Web Design Certification